Guide to the New Yorkers at Work Oral History Collection OH.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- John P. Lundergan, April 9, 1991
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 199)
- James Lustig, June 15, 1981; cuid45110
  - Transcript (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Index (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-110)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-110, Box 25, Audiocassette 71)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 36, Audiocassette 71)
- Bill Lynch, undated; cuid45111
  - Transcript (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-111)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-111, Box 25, Audiocassette 72)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 72)
- Robert MacGregor, December 21, 1988
  - Transcript (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 31, Audiocassette 179A - 179B)
  - Original Recordings (Box 39, Audiocassette 179A - 179B)
- Sam Madell, July 16, 1980; cuid45112
  - Transcript (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Index (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-493 - OH-01-495)
  - Original Recordings (Box 25, Audiocassette 73A - 73C)
- John Maguire, July 18, 1990
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 31, Audiocassette 168A - 168B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 168A - 168B)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_17
- Max Manes, March 2, 1989
  - Transcript (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 29, Audiocassette 145A - 145C)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 38, Audiocassette 145A - 145C)
- Julie Margolin, June 14, 2004
  - Transcript (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-112 - OH-01-114)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-112 - OH-01-113, Box 11, Cd OH-01-114, Box 35, Audiocassette 248A - 248B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 42, Audiocassette 248A - 248B)
- Narciso Martas, June 25, 1996
  - Transcript (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Index (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-115 - OH-01-116)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-115 - OH-01-116, Box 34, Audiocassette 239)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 239)
- Anne B. Martin, September 12, 1995; cuid45113
  - Transcript (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-405 - OH-01-407)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-405 - OH-01-407, Box 30, Audiocassette 156D - 156E)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 156D - 156E)
- George Martin, April 15, 1991
  - Transcript (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 32, Audiocassette 200)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 200)
- Jay Mazur, April 7, 2003; cuid45161
  A transcript of this interview can be found in the Asian Garment Workers in New York City Oral History Collection (OH 018).
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-117)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-117, Box 35, Audiocassette 261)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 42, Audiocassette 261)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_18
- Moore McCormick, July 28, 1980 (Box 29, Audiocassette 141)
- George McDonald, November 29, 1994
  - Transcript (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-450)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 57, Cd OH-01-450)
  - Original Recordings (Box 33, Audiocassette 224)
- Bob McElroy, July 14, 1980; cuid45114
  - Transcript (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Index (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Original Recordings (Box 26, Audiocassette 74A - 74F)
- Bobbie McGee, July 29, 1981
  - Transcript (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-118 - OH-01-119)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-118 - OH-01-119)
  - Original Recordings (Box 26, Audiocassette 75A - 75B)
- Bertha McGowan, September 1, 1981
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-120 - OH-01-121)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-120 - OH-01-121)
  - Original Recordings (Box 29, Audiocassette 143)
- Brian McLaughlin, April 25, 1989 and March 19, 1990
  - Transcript (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-451)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 57, Cd OH-01-451)
- Josie McMillian, January 26, 1981; cuid45115
  - Transcript (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Index (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-122)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-122)
  - Original Recordings (Box 29, Audiocassette 142)
- Joseph McPartlin, April 18, 1991
  - Transcript (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 32, Audiocassette 201)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 201)
- Patricia Meckle, September 6, 1985
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-408 - OH-01-410)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-408 - OH-01-410)
  - Original Recordings (Box 26, Audiocassette 76A - 76C)
- George Meisler, December 12 and December 21, 1979; cuid45116
  - Transcript (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Index (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-411 - OH-01-414)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-411 - OH-01-414)
  - Original Recordings (Box 26, Audiocassette 77A - 77D)
- Susan Metz and Merry Tucker -- Transcript, August 25, 1981; TW_OH_001_ER_19
- Marcella Loring Michelson, June 18, 1980; cuid45117
  - Transcript (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-123)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-123)
  - Original Recordings (Box 26, Audiocassette 79)
- Clarina Michelson, October 20, 1979; cuid45118
  - Transcript (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-296 - OH-01-298)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 54, Cd OH-01-296 - OH-01-298, Box 26, Audiocassette 78A - 78B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 78A - 78B)
- William Michelson, January 15, 1981; cuid45119
  - Transcript (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Index (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-124)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-124, Box 26, Audiocassette 80)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 80)
- Geraldine Miller, June 18, 1981
  - Transcript (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Index (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-125 - OH-01-126)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-125 - OH-01-126)
  - Original Recordings (Box 26, Audiocassette 81)
- Joyce Miller, July 2, 1981; cuid45120
  - Transcript (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-361)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-361)
  - Original Recordings (Box 26, Audiocassette 82)
- Saul Mills, April 3, 1981; cuid45156
  - Transcript (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-127 - OH-01-129)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-127 - OH-01-129, Box 28, Audiocassette 83A - 83B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 83B)
- Eleanor Mishnun, March 22, May 3, and May 22, 1985
  - Transcript (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-299 - OH-01-304)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-299 - OH-01-304)
  - Original Recordings (Box 26, Audiocassette 84A - 84E)
- Queen Mother Moore, December 23, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Walter Morris, October 17, 1980
  - Index (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-130, Box 16, Cd OH-01-131)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-130 - OH-01-131, Box 26, Audiocassette 85)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 85)
- Mary Mullahey, April 20, 1980
  - Transcript (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-132 - OH-01-133)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-132 - OH-01-133)
  - Original Recordings (Box 26, Audiocassette 86)
- T.J. Murphy, May 21, 1997
  - Transcript (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Index (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-383)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-383, Box 34, Audiocassette 240)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 240)
- Al Nash, April 6, 1981
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-362)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-362)
  - Original Recordings (Box 26, Audiocassette 87)
- Pauline Newman, January 19, 1980; cuid45121
  - Transcript (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-208)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 13, Cd OH-01-208, Box 33, Audiocassette 227B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 227A)
- Bernice Nisinson, December 9, 1995 (Box 33, Audiocassette 231)
- No Name, Topic: Fur Cleaning, undated (Box 52, Folder 16)
- No Name, Topic: Furrier Trade Union, undated (Box 52, Folder 15)
- No Name, Topic: Monogramming, undated (Box 52, Folder 14)
- No Name, Topic: Wholesale Flower Workers, undated (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Dolly and John Norman, undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
- John Norman, undated
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 32, Audiocassette 202)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 202)
- Thomas Noschese, October 1, 1980; cuid45122
  - Transcript (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Index (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-415 - OH-01-417)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 57, Cd OH-01-415 - OH-01-417)
  - Original Recordings (Box 26, Audiocassette 88A - 88C)
- Frank Novich National Maritime Union, April 5, 1981
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-350 - OH-01-351)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 55, Cd OH-01-350 - OH-01-351)
  - Original Recordings (Box 37, Audiocassette 89A - 89C)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_20
- William Nuchow, August 6, 1985
  - Notes (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-355)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 55, Cd OH-01-355)
  - Original Recordings (Box 37, Audiocassette 90A - 90B)
  - Partial Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_21
- Thomas O'Brien, July 11, 1984; cuid45157
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-134)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-134)
  - Original Recordings (Box 23, Audiocassette 33)
- Ben Occhiogrosso, July 6, 1981; cuid45123
  - Transcript (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Index (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-135 - OH-01-136)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-135 - OH-01-136)
  - Original Recordings (Box 27, Audiocassette 91)
- Old Westbury, undated
  Cassette 192A is missing as of Fall 2023.
- John O'Neil, July 23, 1980
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-418 - OH-01-419)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 57, Cd OH-01-418 - OH-01-419, Box 27, Audiocassette 92)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 92)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_22
- Celia Orlansky, April 30 and September 23, 1981
  - Transcript (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Index (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-452 - OH-01-453)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 57, Cd OH-01-452 - OH-01-453)
  - Original Recordings (Box 27, Audiocassette 93A - 93C)
- Francis Owens, March 27, 1991
  - Transcript (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-137)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-137, Box 32, Audiocassette 203)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 203)
- Rita Palter, January 17, 1991
  - Transcript (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Index (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-384 - OH-01-385)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-384 - OH-01-385)
  - Original Recordings (Box 31, Audiocassette 170A - 170B)
- Elaine Paul, July 19 and July 22, 1996
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 30, Audiocassette 155A - 155C)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 38, Audiocassette 155A - 155C)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_23
- Solly Pernick, June 16, 1986
  An electronic transcript is available
  - Transcript (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Index (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-138 - OH-01-141)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-138 - OH-01-141)
  - Original Recordings (Box 27, Audiocassette 94A - 94B)
- Beatrice Pflaster, June 5, 1997
  - Transcript (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-142 - OH-01-143)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-142 - OH-01-143, Box 34, Audiocassette 241A - 241B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 241A - 241B)
- Bertram Powers, July 18, 1996
  - Transcript (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Original Recordings (Box 33, Audiocassette 228A - 228B)
- Harold Pryor, March 16, 1989
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 32, Audiocassette 211A - 211C, Box 34, Audiocassette 257A - 257B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 211A - 211C, Box 42, Audiocassette 257A)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_24
- Ida Radosh, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Clarence Reed, April 26, 1986
  - Transcript (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Index (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-226 - OH-01-228)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 13, Cd OH-01-226 - OH-01-228)
  - Original Recordings (Box 27, Audiocassette 95A - 95C)
- Frank Miggs Regina, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Elliot Reif, February 5, 1981 and March 11, 1987; cuid45128
  - Transcript (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Index (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-454 - OH-01-457)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 57, Cd OH-01-454 - OH-01-457, Box 27, Audiocassette 96A - 96D)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 96A - 96B)
- William Reiter, May 29, 1986; cuid45127
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-144)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-144, Box 27, Audiocassette 97)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 97)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_25
- Carlos Rivera and Juan Ponce, June 23, 1981; cuid45129
  - Transcript (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Index (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-363 - OH-01-364)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-363 - OH-01-364)
  - Original Recordings (Box 27, Audiocassette 98)
- Charles Rivers, April 29, 1991; cuid43061
  Duration: 230 minutes in 4 parts; Preservation note: compressed sound leading to "vocal fry" distortion.
  - Transcript (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-229 - OH-01-232)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 13, Cd OH-01-229 - OH-01-231, Box 53, Cd OH-01-232)
  - Original Recordings (Box 40, Audiocassette 190A - 190D)
- Al Robbins, June 30, 1980; cuid45130
  - Transcript (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Index (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-145 - OH-01-147)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-145 - OH-01-147)
  - Original Recordings (Box 27, Audiocassette 99A - 99C)
- Sam Robert, January 12 and January 22, 1990; cuid45131
  - Transcript (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-365 - OH-01-366)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-365 - OH-01-366)
  - Original Recordings (Box 39, Audiocassette 159A - 159B)
- Lillian Roberts, October 27, 1981; cuid43180
  - Transcript (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-395 - OH-01-399)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-395, Box 27, Audiocassette 100)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 100)
- Lillian Roberts, June 9 and June 14, 1999; cuid43181
  - Transcript (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-396 - OH-01-399, Box 34, Audiocassette 253A - 253D)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 42, Audiocassette 253A - 253D)
- Camille Robinson-Gardner, January 26, 1981
  - Transcript (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-311 - OH-01-312)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 54, Cd OH-01-311 - OH-01-312, Box 27, Audiocassette 101)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 101)
- Cleveland Robinson, October 21 and October 28, 1980; cuid45132
  - Transcript (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Index (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-308 - OH-01-310)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 54, Cd OH-01-308 - OH-01-310, Box 27, Audiocassette 102A - 102C)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 102A - 102C)
- Edgar Romney, April 1, 2003; cuid45133
  - Transcript (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-152)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 12, Cd OH-01-152, Box 35, Audiocassette 260)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 42, Audiocassette 260)
- Abe Rosen, April 21, 1980
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 54, Cd OH-01-282 - OH-01-283)
  - Original Recordings (Box 27, Audiocassette 103)
- Michael Rosen, July 20, 1979
  - Transcript (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Index (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-153 - OH-01-154)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 12, Cd OH-01-153 - OH-01-154, Box 27, Audiocassette 104A - 104B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 104A - 104B)
- Morris Rosenszweig, June 29 and September 29, 1980
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-313 - OH-01-316)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 54, Cd OH-01-313, Box 55, Cd OH-01-314 - OH-01-316)
  - Original Recordings (Box 27, Audiocassette 105A - 105B)
- William Ross, February 24 and March 23, 1981; cuid45134
  - Index (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-458 - OH-01-459)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 57, Cd OH-01-458 - OH-01-459)
  - Original Recordings (Box 27, Audiocassette 106A - 106B)
- Betty Bentz Rubin & Jay Rubin, September 6, 1988
  - Transcript (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Index (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Paul Rubin, undated
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-317)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 55, Cd OH-01-317, Box 32, Audiocassette 204)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 204)
- Ernie Rymer, July 19, 1984
  - Transcript (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Index (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-155 - OH-01-156)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 12, Cd OH-01-155 - OH-01-156, Box 27, Audiocassette 107A - 107B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 107A - 107B)
- June Shagalof, undated (Box 50, Folder 9)
- George Schuck, March 24, 1987
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 34, Audiocassette 241C - 241D)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 241C)
- Miriam (and Max) Schwadron, April 30, 1986; cuid45135
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-170 - OH-01-171)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 12, Cd OH-01-170 - OH-01-171, Box 27, Audiocassette 108A)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 108B - 108C)
- Bea Schwartz, May 7 and May 14, 1980; cuid45136
  - Transcript (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-157 - OH-01-158)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 12, Cd OH-01-157 - OH-01-158, Box 27, Audiocassette 109A, Box 28, Audiocassette 109B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 109A - 109B)
- George Schwartz, July 17, August 17, and September 2, 1981; cuid45137
  - Transcript (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Index (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-348 - OH-01-349)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 55, Cd OH-01-348 - OH-01-349)
  - Original Recordings (Box 28, Audiocassette 110A - 110B)
- Thomas Scotland, June 3, 1997; cuid45138
  - Transcript (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Index (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-159 - OH-01-160)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 12, Cd OH-01-159 - OH-01-160, Box 34, Audiocassette 242A - 242B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 242A - 242B)
- Martin Segal, March 3, 1994
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 33, Audiocassette 226)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 226)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_26
- Doris Shaefer, May 27, 1991
  - Transcript (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 32, Audiocassette 205A - 205C)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 205A - 205C)
- Ted Shapiro, June 11, 1998
  - Transcript (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 34, Audiocassette 254A - 254B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 42, Audiocassette 254A - 254B)
- Albert Shanker, April 7, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- John Sheehan, October 19, 1990
  - Notes (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 31, Audiocassette 178)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 178)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_27
- William Shelley, April 30, 1997
  - Index (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-161 - OH-01-162)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 12, Cd OH-01-161 - OH-01-162, Box 34, Audiocassette 243A - 243B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 243A, Box 42, Audiocassette 243B)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_28
- Ken Sherbell, June 25, 1980 and December 12, 1981; cuid45139
  - Transcript (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Index (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-163 - OH-01-165)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 12, Cd OH-01-163 - OH-01-165, Box 28, Audiocassette 111A - 111B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 111B)
- Rebecca Simonson, October 29 and November 10, 1980
  - Index (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-420 - OH-01-424)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 57, Cd OH-01-420 - OH-01-424)
  - Original Recordings (Box 28, Audiocassette 112A - 112C)
- Shirley Simonson, November 19, 1990
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-425)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 57, Cd OH-01-425, Box 32, Audiocassette 208)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 208)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_29
- Lee Singer & Doris Emanuel, October 6, 1980
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-166 - OH-01-167)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 12, Cd OH-01-166 - OH-01-167, Box 28, Audiocassette 113)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 113)
- Pete Smith, undated (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Randall B. Smith, November 5 and December 1, 1980
  - Transcript (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-318 - OH-01-319)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 55, Cd OH-01-318 - OH-01-319)
  - Original Recordings (Box 30, Audiocassette 114A)
- Stanley Smith, June 16, 1981
  - Index (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-168 - OH-01-169)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 12, Cd OH-01-168 - OH-01-169, Box 28, Audiocassette 115)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 115)
- Lily Sokolofsky, April 21, 1980
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-320)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 55, Cd OH-01-320)
  - Original Recordings (Box 28, Audiocassette 116)
- Jackie Stack, June 11, 1981
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-321)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 55, Cd OH-01-321, Box 31, Audiocassette 185)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 185)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_30
- Joe Stack, September 5 and November 5, 1981
  - Transcript (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-323 - OH-01-328)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 55, Cd OH-01-323 - OH-01-328)
  - Original Recordings (Box 28, Audiocassette 118A - 118C)
- Monroe & Matilda Stein, February 11, 1979
  - Transcript (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Index (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-481 - OH-01-482, OH-01-487 - OH-01-488)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 58, Cd OH-01-481 - OH-01-482, OH-01-487 - OH-01-488)
  - Original Recordings (Box 28, Audiocassette 117A - 117B)
- Leon Sverdlove, October 23, 1979
  - Transcript (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-329 - OH-01-334)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 54, Cd OH-01-329 - OH-01-334)
  - Original Recordings (Box 28, Audiocassette 120A - 120C)
- Loretta Szeliga, August 11, 1981
  - Index (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-335 - OH-01-340)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 55, Cd OH-01-335 - OH-01-340, Box 28, Audiocassette 119A - 119C)
  - Original Audiocassettes (Box 37, Audiocassette 119A - 119C)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_31
- Ruth Kessler Taylor, November 22, 1981
  - Transcript (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Index (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-444 - OH-01-449)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 57, Cd OH-01-444 - OH-01-449)
  - Original Recordings (Box 28, Audiocassette 121A - 121C)
- Hyman Teitelbaun, May 12, 1982
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-172 - OH-01-175)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 12, Cd OH-01-172 - OH-01-175, Box 28, Audiocassette 122A - 122B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 38, Audiocassette 122A - 122B)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_32
- David Tolan, August 1, 1980
  - Transcript (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-343 - OH-01-344)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 55, Cd OH-01-343 - OH-01-344)
  - Original Recordings (Box 28, Audiocassette 123)
- Ida Torres, June 24, 1980; cuid45140
  - Transcript (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Access CDs (Box 16, Cd OH-01-176 - OH-01-177)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 12, Cd OH-01-176 - OH-01-177)
  - Original Recordings (Box 28, Audiocassette 124)
- Mary Tucker and Susan Metz, August 25, 1981; cuid14390
  - Index (Box 51, Folder 5)